Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
circa 1980-2004
Clark, Dick, 1929-2012.
360 linear ft.
Audiotapes of more than 2000 radio broadcasts; shows include Rock, Roll and Remember, Dick Clark in Hollywood, National Music Survey and more. Collection also includes a few video tapes of televisions specials, published books, back issues of TV Guide, scrapbooks, clippings, scripts for radio shows, and more.
3647883
Biographical History
Dick Clark (1929-2012) was an American radio and television personality. Over the course of his career he hosted radio shows (Dick Clark Radio Show; Rock, Roll and Remember; Dick Clark National Music Survey), game shows (Pyramid) and television shows and specials, including American Bandstand and his own Dick Clark Show, which ran on Saturday nights from 1958 to 1960. His company dick clark productions [sic], founded in 1957, has produced shows, specials and movies ranging from classic to contemporary, such as American Bandstand (1952-1989) and the popular So You Think You Can Dance. The company was sold in 2007 and as of 2020 is part of entertainment conglomerate MRC under their Live & Alternative division.
Clark was a founding partner of the United Stations radio company. With Nick Verbitsky, Chief Operating Officer at Mutual Radio, Clark formed the company in 1981, and among the company's first shows was Dick Clark's Rock, Roll & Remember. Within twelve years United Stations had become one of America's top three radio networks. By 1994 the company had acquired or merged with several others, including RKO Radio Networks, and was renamed Unistar Communications. In 1994 Clark and Verbitsky resurrected the original name and formed the United Stations Radio Networks; today USRN is the largest independently owned and operated radio network in America and provides comedy writing, production and talent services to more than 600 stations.
Clark is perhaps best known for his annual appearance as host of Dick Clark's New Year's Rockin' Eve, broadcast live from Times Square in New York every December 31 since 1972. Although a stroke in December of 2004 prevented him from hosting that year, he returned in 2005 and continued to host the show with Ryan Seacrest until his death in 2012. Clark received numerous awards and recognitions for his contributions to the profession, including four Emmys and a Peabody; induction into the National Radio Hall of Fame, the Broadcasting Magazine Hall of Fame and the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame; and a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Dick Clark Papers includes correspondence, interviews, proposals, scripts, and recordings.
Correspondence contains only a few letters and notes.
Interviews consists of notes and recordings. The notes are from interviews primarily with musicians: singers, songwriters, band members, record producers, and so on. Some are annotated with the show on which the interview aired. These are in alphabetical order by name, beginning with "M"; folders for A through L were not included in the donated collection. The recordings, on audiocassettes, are primarily with movie and television actors.
Proposals for Clark's company, dick clark productions [sic], include a game show, a television episode, and a radio show.
The majority of the collection consists of Recordings of Dick Clark's most well-known and long-running radio programs.
Recordings, Countdown America (approximately 470 episodes) began in 1986 as a four-hour show counting down the Top 30 hits of the day. The show switched to three hours in 1991 and reduced its coverage to the Top 20 hits. Clark began hosting the show in late 1985. The show continued until the weekend of December 31, 1994, when its name was changed to Dick Clark’s U.S. Music Survey (see below).
Recordings, Dick Clark in Hollywood (approximately 500 episodes) was a series of ninety-second (1:30) reports hosted by Dick Clark, consisting of interviews with Hollywood actors, writer, directors etc. Most of the interviews were conducted by radio department personnel, with introductions written to create the illusion that Clark had done the interview personally (for example, Clark's intro might say, "Tom Hanks has a new movie out and when he stopped by I asked him about his early days starring in Bosom Buddies.") The show ran from February 20, 1989 to July 15, 1990.
Recordings, Dick Clark's Music Machine (approximately 80 episodes) was a three-hour oldies show that aired in the mid-1970s. The first hour was oldies, the second hour was current hits, and the third hour was up and coming music and artists. The Oldies Hour was much more popular than the other two hours and eventually became its own show, Dick Clark's Solid Gold (see below).
Recordings, Dick Clark's National Music Survey (approximately 230 episodes) was created in 1981 by Dick Clark for the Mutual Broadcasting System. The show counted down the top 30 contemporary hits of the week in direct competition with American Top 40.
Recordings, Dick Clark's Solid Gold (approximately 350 episodes) was a one-hour "oldies" show, a spin-off of the popular oldies hour on The Dick Clark Music Machine.
Recordings, Dick Clark's U.S. Music Survey (approximately 360 episodes) was the successor to Countdown America. It began airing the weekend of January 7-8, 1995 and continued until December 2004 with Dick Clark as host. Following Clark’s stroke in December of 2004, voiceover talent Jeff Robins filled in briefly, followed by permanent guest host Mark Wallengren of Los Angeles radio station KOST-FM. Wllengren hosted the show until it ceased production in December 2005.
Recordings, Rock, Roll and Remember (approximately 1000 episodes) began in 1982. Gene Weed appears as co-host from show #002 (February 20-21, 1982) to show #048 (Jan 8-9, 1983) and Mark Elliot appears as co-host from show #049 (Jan 15-16, 1983) to show #194 (Oct 26-27, 1985). Dick Clark is the only host as of show #195 (November 2-3, 1985). The last original show with Clark aired the weekend of January 1-2, 2005 (pre-recorded shortly before his stroke). After that date, the show continued in syndication with repeat episodes from the archives. It currently (as of 2013) airs on stations around the country.
Recordings, Specials and one-time shows (approximately 100 items) include the American Music Awards, American Country Music Awards, and specials on specific artists or themes (Beach Boys, Elvis, Pat Benatar, Journey, Golden Years of Motown, Top 30 Artists of All Time, Dick Clark's Summer Memories, etc.). A variety of formats are represented, from reels to large-format BetaMax and VHS.
More than 40 Scrapbooks contain clippings covering Clark's life, work, and career.
Scripts consists of annotated scripts for several hundred episodes of Countdown America, Rock Roll and Remember, and the US Music Survey, as well as for a few specials such as the American Country Music Awards. Many of these also include cue sheets (lists of commercial spots).
[Portions of this description generously provided by Jim Zoller, producer, writer and engineer at Dick Clark Productions for more than twenty years.]
Arrangement of the Collection
Within each series, material is ordered alphabetically by show title. Within each show, episodes are ordered chronologically.
Separated Material
More than 150 issues of Rolling Stone have been transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate these items.
Subject and Genre Headings
Music; Popular culture; Radio, television, film; Clark, Dick, 1929-2012.; Dick Clark Productions (Firm); Rock, Roll and Remember (Radio program); Countdown America (Radio program); Dick Clark in Hollywood (Radio program); Dick Clark's Solid Gold (Radio program); Dick Clark's Music Machine (Radio program); Dick Clark's National Music Survey (Radio program); Radio broadcasters -- United States.; Television personalities -- United States.; Television producers and directors -- United States.; Disc jockeys -- United States.; Variety shows (Television programs); Country music music -- United States -- History.; Rock music -- United States -- History.; Radio broadcasting -- United States -- History.; Popular culture -- United States.; Popular music -- United States.; Television specials -- Country music.; Television specials -- Rock music.; Television specials -- Awards.; Audiotapes.; Clippings (information artifacts); Scrapbooks.; Sound recordings.; Videotapes.; Radio broadcasters.; Television personalities.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Access to recordings requires advance notice in order for staff to produce a use copy.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dick Clark, 2009.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- Interviews
  - Notes
    - A, C, J miscellaneous, Abba, Commodores, Elton John, Wynonna Judd (Box 1)
    - Alan Parsons Project, See Parsons, Alan.
    - Bailey, Tom, See Thompson Twins.
    - Ballard, Glenn, See Wilson Phillips.
    - Barnes, Don, See 38 Special.
    - Bass, Lance, See N Sync.
    - Beatles, See McCartney, Paul; Starr, Ringo
    - Bentyne, Cheryl, See Manhattan Transfer.
    - Bickler, Dave, See Survivor.
    - Blades, Jack, See Night Ranger.
    - Carlisi, Jeff, See 38 Special.
    - Carmichael, Jesse, See Maroon 5.
    - Chapman, Beth Nielsen (Box 1)
    - Chaquico, Craig, See Starship.
    - Clemons, Clarence, See Springsteen, Bruce.
    - Connell, Andy, See Swing Out Sister.
    - Crofts, Dash (Darrell), See Seals and Crofts.
    - Cronin, Kevin, See REO Speedwagon.
    - Currie, Alannah, See Thompson Twins.
    - Darwish, Tiffany, See Tiffany.
    - Davis, Clive, See Santana.
    - DeYoung, Dennis, See Styx.
    - Dittrich, John, See Restless Heart.
    - Doughty, Neil, See REO Speedwagon.
    - Drewery, Corinne, See Swing Out Sister.
    - Droubay, Mark, See Survivor.
    - Dusik, Ryan, See Maroon 5.
    - E Street Band, See Springsteen, Bruce.
    - Edwards, Dennis, See Temptations.
    - Fatone, Joey, See N Sync.
    - Fitzgerald, Alan "Fitz", See Night Ranger.
    - Gordy, Berry, See Wonder, Stevie.
    - Greenspoon, Jimmy, See Three Dog Night.
    - Hall, Bruce, See REO Speedwagon.
    - Hatfield, Bobby, See Righteous Brothers.
    - Hauser, Tim, See Manhattan Transfer.
    - Hayes, Darren, See Savage Garden.
    - Hayward, Justin, See Moody Blues.
    - Hucknall, Mick, See Simply Red.
    - Innis, Dave, See Restless Heart.
    - Jackson, Bernard, See Surface.
    - Jagger, Mick, See Rolling Stones.
    - Jamison, Jimi, See Survivor.
    - Jefferson Starship, See Starship.
    - Jennings, Greg, See Restless Heart.
    - Kendricks, Eddie, See Temptations.
    - King, William, See A, C, J miscellaneous.
    - Lambert, Dennis, See Starship.
    - Levine, Adam, See Maroon 5.
    - Lodge, John, See Moody Blues.
    - Lukather, Steve, See Toto.
    - Madonna (Box 1)
    - Manchester, Melissa (Box 1)
    - Manhattan Transfer (Box 1)
    - Manilow, Barry (Box 1)
    - Maroon 5 (Box 1)
    - Marx, Richard (Box 1)
    - Mary Jane Girls (Box 1)
    - Matchbox 20 (Box 1)
    - Mathis, Johnny (Box 1)
    - Mayer, John (Box 1)
    - McBride, Martina (Box 1)
    - McCartney, Paul (Box 1)
    - McDonald, Michael (Box 1)
    - McDuffie, Jojo, See Mary Jane Girls.
    - McGraw, Tim (Box 1)
    - McKnight, Brian (Box 1)
    - McLachlan, Saran (Box 1)
    - Medley, Bill, See Righteous Brothers.
    - Mellencamp, John (Box 1)
    - Mendes, Sergio (Box 1)
    - Messina, Jimmy, See Poco.
    - Michaels, George (Box 1)
    - Midler, Bette (Box 1)
    - Moody Blues (Box 1)
    - Murray, Ann (Box 1)
    - M, misc (Box 1)
    - N Sync (Box 2)
    - Nash, Leigh, See Sixpence None the Richer.
    - Neville, Aaron (Box 2)
    - Newton-John, Olivia (Box 2)
    - Nicks, Stevie (Box 2)
    - Night Ranger (Box 2)
    - Nilsson, Harry (Box 2)
    - N, misc (Box 2)
    - Ocean, Billy (Box 2)
    - Orbison, Roy (Box 2)
    - Orlando, Tony (Box 2)
    - Orzabal, Roland, See Tears for Fears.
    - Osborne, Jeffrey (Box 2)
    - Osmond, Donny (Box 2)
    - O, misc (Box 2)
    - Page. Martin (Box 2)
    - Palmer, Robert (Box 2)
    - Panozzo, Chuck, See Styx.
    - Parker, Ray Jt. (Box 2)
    - Parr, John (Box 2)
    - Parsons, Alan (Box 2)
    - Parton, Dolly (Box 2)
    - Pet Shop Boys (Box 2)
    - Peterik, Jim, See Survivor.
    - Phillips, Chynna, See Wilson Phillips.
    - Poco (Box 2)
    - Pointer Sisters (Box 2)
    - Porcaro, Steve, See Toto.
    - Post, Mike (Box 2)
    - Presley, Elvis (Box 2)
    - P, misc (Box 2)
    - Raitt, Bonnie (Box 2)
    - REO Speedwagon (Box 2)
    - Restless Heart (Box 2)
    - Rice, Tim, See A, C, J miscellaneous.
    - Richards, Keith, See Rolling Stones.
    - Richie, Lionel (Box 2)
    - Righteous Brothers (Box 2)
    - Riley, Melvin (Box 2)
    - Rimes, Leann (Box 2)
    - Robinson, Smokey (Box 2)
    - Rogers, Kenny (Box 2)
    - Rolie, Gregg, See Santana.
    - Rolling Stones (Box 2)
    - Ronstadt, Linda (Box 3)
    - Ross, Diana (Box 3)
    - Roth, David Lee (Box 3)
    - Roxette (Box 3)
    - Russell, Brenda (Box 3)
    - Rutherford, Mike (Box 3)
    - R, misc (Box 3)
    - Sade (Box 3)
    - Santana (Box 3)
    - Savage Garden (Box 3)
    - Scaggs, Boz (Box 3)
    - Scandal (Box 3)
    - Seals and Crofts (Box 3)
    - Secada, Jon (Box 3)
    - Seger, Bob (Box 3)
    - Shaw, Tommy, See Styx.
    - Shepard, Vonda (Box 3)
    - Shrieve, Michael, See Santana.
    - Siegel, Janis, See Manhattan Transfer.
    - Simon, Carly (Box 3)
    - Simon, Paul (Box 3)
    - Simply Red (Box 3)
    - Sixpence None the Richer (Box 3)
    - Smith, Curt, See Tears for Fears.
    - Smith, Michael W. (Box 3)
    - Smyth, Patty, See also Scandal. (Box 3)
    - Springfield, Rick (Box 3)
    - Springsteen, Bruce (Box 3)
    - Starr, Ringo (Box 3)
    - Starship (Box 3)
    - Stewart, Al (Box 3)
    - Stewart, Larry, See Restless Heart.
    - Stewart, Rod (Box 3)
    - Stigers, Curtis (Box 3)
    - Sting (Box 3)
    - Styx (Box 3)
    - Summer, Donna (Box 3)
    - Supremes (Box 3)
    - Surface (Box 3)
    - Survivor (Box 3)
    - Swing Out Sister (Box 4)
    - S, misc (Box 4)
    - Taylor, James (Box 4)
    - Taylor, Livingston (Box 4)
    - Tears for Fears (Box 4)
    - Temptations (Box 4)
    - Tennant, Neil, See Pet Shop Boys.
    - Tesh, John (Box 4)
    - 38 Special (Box 4)
    - Thomas, B.J. (Box 4)
    - Thomas, Mickey, See Starship.
    - Thomas, Rob, See Matchbox 20.
    - Thompson Twins (Box 4)
    - Three Dog Night (Box 4)
    - Tiffany (Box 4)
    - Tomlinson, Michael (Box 4)
    - Toto (Box 4)
    - Townshend, Pete (Box 4)
    - Troccoli, Kathy (Box 4)
    - Turner, Tina (Box 4)
    - Twain, Shania (Box 4)
    - T, misc (Box 4)
    - U, misc (Box 4)
    - Vandross, Luther (Box 4)
    - Vanelli, Gino (Box 4)
    - Vera, Billy (Box 4)
    - V, misc (Box 4)
    - Wagner, Jack (Box 4)
    - Waite, John (Box 4)
    - Walden, Narada Michael (Box 4)
    - Warnes, Jennifer (Box 4)
    - Warren, Dianne (Box 4)
    - Warwick, Dionne (Box 4)
    - Watson, Jeff, See Night Ranger.
    - Weinberg, Max, See Springsteen, Bruce.
    - Wells, Corey, See Three Dog Night.
    - Wham!, See Michaels, George.
    - Who, See Townshend, Pete.
    - Williams, Deniece (Box 4)
    - Williams, Joseph, See Toto.
    - Williams, Otis, See Temptations.
    - Williams, Vanessa (Box 4)
    - Wilson Phillips (Box 4)
    - Wilson, Brian, See Wilson Phillips.
    - Wilson, Carnie, See Wilson Phillips.
    - Wilson, Mary, See Supremes.
    - Wilson, Wendy, See Wilson Phillips.
    - Winwood, Steve (Box 4)
    - Wonder, Stevie (Box 4)
    - Woods, Ron, See Rolling Stones.
    - W, misc (Box 5)
    - Young, Paul (Box 5)
    - Young, Rusty, See Poco.
    - Y, misc (Box 5)
    - Cut sheets, unused, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Non-musical interviews, actors, comedians, directors, writers, etc.; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Recordings
    - Aames, Willie, 03-15-1989; clark_d_001; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - ACMA [Academy of Country Music Awards] Interviews, 04-1985; clark_d_002; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Akins, Claude, 07-07-1989; clark_d_003; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Albano, Lou, 07-27-1989; clark_d_004; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Albert, Edward, 12-05-1989; clark_d_005; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Alda, Alan, 06-16-1990; clark_d_006; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Alfonso, Kristian, 02-24-1986; clark_d_007; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Allen, Byron, 04-02-1984; clark_d_008; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Allen, Steve, 02-28-1989; clark_d_009; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - AMA [American Music Awards] interviews, 1985; clark_d_010; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Arvesan, Nina, 12-01-1989; clark_d_011; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Aykroyd, Dan, 1984; clark_d_012; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bach, Catherine, 06-22-1989; clark_d_013; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bacharach, Bert, See Bergman; Bacharach.
    - Badler, Jane, 06-29-1989; clark_d_014; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bagdasarian, Ross; Karman, Janice; The Chipmunks, [undated]; clark_d_051; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Baio, Scott, 03-15-1989; clark_d_015; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Baker, Ray, 04-11-1990; clark_d_016; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bakula, Scott, 08-10-1989; clark_d_017; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Barri, Steve, 10-09-1984; clark_d_018; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Barry, Jeff, 10-01-1984; clark_d_019; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bauer, Steven, 12-19-1989; clark_d_020; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bean, Michael, 07-31-1989; clark_d_021; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Beauer, Jim, 09-12-1989; clark_d_022; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Becker, Tony, 07-25-1989; clark_d_024; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bega, Leslie, 02-23-1989; clark_d_023; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bell, Daryl, 09-21-1989; clark_d_025; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bellamy, Ralph, 12-13-1989; clark_d_026; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bennett, Fran, Mar 23 [no year]; clark_d_032; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Berg, Scott, 05-04-1989; clark_d_027; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bergen, Polly, 04-04-1990; clark_d_028; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bergman, Jo, 11-20-1984; clark_d_029; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bergman; Bacharach, 10-11-1984; clark_d_030; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bernstein, Carl, 1989; clark_d_031; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bettis, John, 06-20-1985; clark_d_033; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bohay, Heidi, 09-22-1989; clark_d_034; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Boone, Pat, 10-31-1989; clark_d_036; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Booth, Pat, 07-21-1989; clark_d_035; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Boothe, Powers, [undated]; clark_d_037; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bradbury, Ray, [undated]; clark_d_038; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Brett, Jeremy, 01-05-1990; clark_d_039; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Bullock, Sandra, 04-16-1990; clark_d_040; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Burke, Chris, 02-12-1990; clark_d_041; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Buttram, Pat, 04-26-1990; clark_d_042; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Byrnes, Jim, Apr 25 [no year]; clark_d_043; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Candy, John, 05-26-1989; clark_d_044; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Carmen, Julie, 05-05-1989; clark_d_046; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Carr, Jane, 03-12-1990; clark_d_045; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Carter, Thomas, 02-16-1990; clark_d_047; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Casella, Max, 05-09-1990; clark_d_048; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Charleson, Leslie, Mar 14 [no year]; clark_d_049; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Chen, Joan, 05-03-1990; clark_d_050; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Child Find, 02-14-1985; clark_d_085; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - The Chipmunks, See Bagdasarian, Ross; Karman, Janice; The Chipmunks.
    - Clark, Mary Higgins, 05-17-1989; clark_d_052; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Clooney, George, Jun 17 [no year]; clark_d_053; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Coleman, Dabney, 04-23-1990; clark_d_054; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Connery, Sean #1, See Neufeld, Mace; Connery Sean #1.
    - Connery, Sean #2, [undated]; clark_d_055; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Conrad, Robert, 01-11-1990; clark_d_056; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Conti, Bill, 10-16-1989; clark_d_057; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Coulier, David, 04-14-1989; clark_d_058; Audio cassette (Box 167)
    - Cranston, Alan, 05-31-1984; clark_d_059; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Craven, Wes, 10-06-1989; clark_d_060; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Crosby, Cathy Lee, 02-09-1989; clark_d_061; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Crosby, Norm, 07-07-1989; clark_d_062; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Crowe, Tonya, 09-22-1989; clark_d_063; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - DeLorenzo, Michael, 09-19-1989; clark_d_064; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - DeLuise, Dom, 03-02-1989; clark_d_065; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - DeLuise, Peter, 06-28-1989; clark_d_066; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Despie, [Dennis] and Miziker, [Ron], 12-21-1989; clark_d_067; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Devito, Danny, 05-17-1984; clark_d_068; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Diller, Phyllis, May 15 [no year]; clark_d_069; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Disney, Roy, [undated]; clark_d_070; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Douglas, Steve, 07-11-1984; clark_d_071; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Down, Lesley-Anne [misspelled on label as Leslie Ann], 12-04-1989; clark_d_072; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Dreesen, Tom [misspelled on label as Dressan], Apr 19 [no year]; clark_d_073; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Dryer, Fred [misspelled on label as Dreyer], 04-18-1989; clark_d_074; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Duart, Louise, 10-31-1989; clark_d_075; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Duncan, Sandy, [undated]; clark_d_076; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Dunn, Dennis, 07-05-1989; clark_d_077; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Edwards, Anthony, 01-10-1990; clark_d_078; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Elwes, Cary, 06-06-1990; clark_d_079; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Evigan, Greg, 04-05-1989; clark_d_080; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Fabares, Shelley [misspelled on label as Shelly], 02-07-1990; clark_d_081; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Falk, Peter: Profile on Peter Falk "Columbo", [undated]; clark_d_082; Audio cassette (Box 168)
      Radio Links: 3:30 and :90
    - Farr, Jamie, 03-27-1984; clark_d_083; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Ferrigno, Lou [misspelled on label as Fergino], Apr 22 [no year]; clark_d_084; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Firth, Colin, [undated]; clark_d_086; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Flannigan, Maureen: Out of This World [misspelled on label as Flanagan], [undated]; clark_d_087; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Foray, June, 03-01-1990; clark_d_091; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Forsyth, William, Mar 21 [no year]; clark_d_088; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Foster, Kimberly, 09-19-1989; clark_d_089; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Fox, Michael J., 04-05-1984; clark_d_090; accompanying note; Audio cassette (Box 168)